A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1 FA1292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Grants, 1951-1996, 2002; 2
  - 59-474-31, University of Indonesia, Fellow, Sutomo, Tjokronegoro, 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 598)
  - 70-141-26, University of Indonesia, Fellow, Tjahjadi, Gunawan, 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 599)
  - 62-647-45, University of Indonesia, Fellow, Tobing, Alexander, 1963-1964 (Box 47, Folder 600)
  - 60-541-49, University of Indonesia, Fellow, Utama, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 601)
  - CM 273, CM 340, University of Indonesia, Visiting Professor, Schultz, Edwin W., 1952-1955 (Box 47, Folder 602)
  - CM 361, University of Indonesia, Visiting Professor, Schultz, Edwin W., 1956-1957 (Box 47, Folder 603)
  - 57-417, 59-495, 60-544, University of Indonesia, Visiting Professor, Schultz, Edwin W., 1957-1961 (Box 47, Folder 604)
  - 57-409, University of Indonesia, Visiting Professor, Smetana, Hans, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 605)
  - CM 274, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Pathology Building, 1951-1952, 1954-1960 (Box 47, Folder 606)
  - CM 297, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Physiology, 1953-1955 (Box 47, Folder 607)
  - CM 321, CM 331, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Cardiorespiratory Laboratory, 1954-1956 (Box 47, Folder 608)
  - CM 389, University of Hong Kong, Journals, 1956-1959 (Box 48, Folder 609)
  - 57-407, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Physiology, 1957-1959 (Box 48, Folder 610)
  - 57-420, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Research, Obstetrics & Gynecology, 1957-1959 (Box 48, Folder 611)
  - 58-427, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Pharmacology Student Laboratory, 1958-1960 (Box 48, Folder 612)
  - 58-428, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Anatomy, 1957-1960 (Box 48, Folder 613)
  - 58-447, University of Hong Kong, Equipment & Furnishings-Medical Library Branch, 1958-1960 (Box 48, Folder 614)
  - 58-458, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Radioisotope Laboratory, 1958, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 615)
  - 59-486, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Anatomy, Biochemistry, Pathology, Obstetrics & Gynecology, 1958-1961 (Box 48, Folder 616)
  - 60-529, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Surgery & Bacteriology, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 617)
  - 61-575, University of Hong Kong, Equipment, 1961-1963 (Box 48, Folder 618)
  - 61-614, University of Hong Kong, Equipment & Supplies-Preclinical, 1961-1962 (Box 48, Folder 619)
  - 62-670,University of Hong Kong, Building Construction & Equipment-Medical Library & Student Center, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 620)
    2014:022, SG 1:035
  - 62-6702, University of Hong Kong, Building Construction & Equipment-Medical Library & Student Center, 1962-1963, 1966; 2014:022, SG1:035
  - 62-671, University of Hong Kong, Research-Pediatrics, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 621)
  - 63-728, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Obstetrics & Gynecology, Pediatrics, 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 622)
  - 63-682, University of Hong Kong, Equipment & Supplies, 1963-1965 (Box 48, Folder 623)
  - 64-752, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Pathology, 1964-1967 (Box 48, Folder 624)
  - 64-786, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Supplies, X-rays, 1964-1968 (Box 48, Folder 625)
  - 64-787, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Experimental Surgery, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1964-1967 (Box 48, Folder 626)
  - 64-788, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Radioisotope, 1964-1968 (Box 48, Folder 627)
  - 65-805, University of Hong Kong, Temperature Control Equipment, 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 628)
  - 65-824, University of Hong Kong, Research-Anatomy, 1964-1965, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 629)
  - 65-823, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Anatomy, Physiology, Orthopedics, 1965-1969 (Box 48, Folder 630)
  - 65-844, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Obstetrics & Gynecology, 1965-1970 (Box 48, Folder 631)
  - 65-857, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Animal Quarters, 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 632)
  - 66-887, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Anatomy, Physiology, 1965-1969 (Box 49, Folder 633)
  - 66-888, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Pharmacology, 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 634)
  - 66-918, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Physiology, Pharmacology Laboratory, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1966-1968 (Box 49, Folder 635)
  - 66-919, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Pediatrics, 1966-1969 (Box 49, Folder 636)
  - 67-949, University of Hong Kong, Library Support, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 637)
  - 67-979, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Pediatrics, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 638)
  - 68-015, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Medicine, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 639)
  - 68-044, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-Anatomy, Pharmacology, Surgery, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 640)
  - 69-075, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 641)
  - 69-105, University of Hong Kong, Calculating Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 642)
  - 70-131, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 643)
  - 70-161, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 644)
  - 71-188, University of Hong Kong, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-4974 (Box 49, Folder 645)
  - 71-219, University of Hong Kong, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1974 (Box 49, Folder 646)
  - 72-252 I, University of Hong Kong, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 647)
  - 72-281 I, University of Hong Kong, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1978 (Box 49, Folder 648)
  - 73-319, University of Hong Kong, Endowment Fund for Research, Accounting of Expenditures, 1976-1993 (Box 49, Folder 649)
  - 73-319, University of Hong Kong, Endowment Fund for Research, General Correspondence, 1973-1974, 1976-1978, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 650)
  - 73-319, University of Hong Kong, Endowment Fund for Research, General Correspondence, 1973-1974, 1976-1978, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 650A)
  - 76-349, University of Hong Kong, School of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1976-1989, 1991-1993 (Box 50, Folder 651-652)
  - 76-350, University of Hong Kong, School of Medicine, Postgraduate Medical Education, 1976, 1978-1984 (Box 50, Folder 653)
  - 76-350, University of Hong Kong, School of Medicine, General Correspondence, Regional Fellows, 1976-1983, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 654)
  - 63-694-40, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Braga, Carolina Augusta, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 655)
  - 63-694-36, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Brodetti, Alfredo, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 656)
  - 58-429-2, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Chan, Shuk Tsz, 1958-1959 (Box 50, Folder 657)
  - 72-266-7, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Chan, Tai Kwong, 1971-1973 (Box 50, Folder 658)
  - 66-896-45, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Chan, Woon Cheung, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 659)
  - 59-474-15, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Chang, K. S. Francis, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 660)
  - CM 311-5, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Chang, Kuang-pi Stephen, 1954-1955 (Box 50, Folder 661)
  - 61-591-17, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Cheng, Kwok-Kew, 1961-1961 (Box 51, Folder 662)
  - 59-474-14, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Chun, Daphne Wai-chan, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 663)
  - 71-203-5, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Chung, Euphine Yiu-Fun, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 664)
  - 60-541-5, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Fung, Joseph Hon Yin, 1960, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 665)
  - CM 241-2, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Gould, Donald W., 1951-1952 (Box 51, Folder 666)
  - CM 327-18, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Hodgson, Arthur R, 1956-1958 (Box 51, Folder 667)
  - CM 327-5, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Hsieh, W. Arnold Chia Loh, 1955, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 668)
  - 62-647-11, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Hsieh, W. Arnold Chia Loh, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 669)
  - CM 362-19, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Huang, Chi-to, 1957-1958 (Box 51, Folder 670)
  - 58-429-3, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Huang, Esther Ying-yu, 1958, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 671)
  - CM 327-19, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Hui, Kenneth Kwan-lun, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 672)
  - 69-086-23, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Ip, Shing Kwan, 1969-1971 (Box 51, Folder 673)
  - CM 279-19, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Jones, Howell W. P., 1954-1955 (Box 51, Folder 673)
  - 68-022-7, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Kan, Lai-Bing, 1968-1969 (Box 51, Folder 675)
  - 58-429-4, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Kan, Pun Shui, 1958, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 676)
  - 68-022-35, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Koo, Chia Gee, 1968-1969 (Box 51, Folder 677)
  - 57-397-28, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Kwaam, Hau Cheong, 1958-1959 (Box 51, Folder 678)
  - 65-834-20, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Kwong, Kwok-Hay, 1965-1967 (Box 51, Folder 679)
  - CM 327-22, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Lee, Marjorie Mo Chueh, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 681)
  - 64-762-57, 65-868-5, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Lee, Marjorie Mo Chueh, 1958, 1962, 1964-1966 (Box 51, Folder 682)
  - 70-141-58, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Leong, Edward Che-Hung, 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 683)
  - 63-694-20, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Li, Franklin Wang-Pong, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 684)
  - 67-936-13, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Low, Weng Djin, 1964-1965, 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 685)
  - Cm 259-12, 279-10, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, McFadzean, Alexander James Smith, 1953-1954 (Box 51, Folder 686)
  - 63-694-50, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Mo, Benjamin Pui-Nin, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 687)
  - CM 259-13 CM 311-3, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Pan, Joseph Yin-chi, 1953-1954 (Box 51, Folder 688)
  - CM 311-8, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Pang, Lillian, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 589)
  - CM 311-9, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Skinsnes, Olaf K., 1953, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 690)
  - 58-429-21, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Stock, Francis E., 1959 (Box 51, Folder 691)
  - CM 241-3, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Teoh, Tiaw Bee, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 692)
  - 63-694-12, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Todd, David, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 694)
  - 69-086-42, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Todd, David, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 693)
  - CM 311-4, CM 327-7, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Tsang, Kam Chin, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 695)
  - 68-011-12, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Tsao, Yen Chow, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 696)
  - 67-938-20, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Tso, Shiu Chiu, 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 697)
  - 70-141-33, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Wang, James Chi-Ching, 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 698)
  - 62-624, University of Hong Kong, Research Fellow, Way, E. Leong, 1961-1963 (Box 52, Folder 699)
  - 67-938-30, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Yau, Arthur Charles Meng Choy, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 700)
  - 70-141-6, 70-141-37, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Yeung, Kwok-Keung, 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 701)
  - 67-938-28, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Yeung (Young), Rose T. T., 1966-1970 (Box 52, Folder 702)
  - 69-08-16, 70-141-2, University of Hong Kong, Fellow, Yu, Donald Yu-Chiu, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 703)
  - 73-318-8, 73-318-14, University of Hong Kong, School of Medicine, Fellowship Allocation, 1973-1975, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 704)
  - 73-329-3, 78-329-18, University of Hong Kong, School of Medicine, Fellowship Allocation, 1974-1983 (Box 52, Folder 705)
  - 73-329-20, University of Hong Kong, School of Medicine, Fellowship, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 706)
  - 75-343-7, University of Hong Kong, School of Medicine, Fellowship, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 707)
  - 68-825, University of Hong Kong, Visiting Reader in Pathology, Catto, Mary, 1965-1966 (Box 52, Folder 708)
  - 59-517, University of Hong Kong, Visiting Professor, Colonia, Paul C., 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 709)
  - Cm 266, University of Hong Kong, Visiting Professor, Dunlap, Albert M., 1952-1955 (Box 52, Folder 710)
  - 63-711, University of Hong Kong, Visiting Professor, Duthie, Robert B., 1963-1965 (Box 52, Folder 711)
  - CM 339, University of Hong Kong, Visiting Professor, Eastman, Nicholson J., 1955-1956 (Box 52, Folder 712)
  - 67-937, University of Hong Kong, Visiting Lecturer (Orthopedic Surgery), Hoaglund, Franklin T., 1966-1969 (Box 52, Folder 713)
  - CM 348, University of Hong Kong, Visiting Professor (Pathology), van Dyke, H. B., 1955-1957 (Box 53, Folder 714)
  - 74-340, National Taiwan University (NTU), School of Medicine, Postgraduate & Continuing Education, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 715)
  - 78-373-6, National Taiwan University (NTU), School of Medicine, Fellowship Allocation, 1979-1983 (Box 53, Folder 716)
  - 76-356, NTU, School of Medicine, Postgraduate & Continuing Education, 1976-1983 (Box 53, Folder 716)
  - 67-938-47, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Biak, Sang Ho, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 717)
  - CM 259-19, CM 311-17, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Chang, Suk Chul, 1953-1955 (Box 53, Folder 718)
  - 68-022-31, 69-086-45, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Chang, Woo Hyun, 1968-1971 (Box 53, Folder 719)
  - 66-896-59, 67-938-54, 68-022-54, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, (Choi) Lee, Eun Ok, 1967-1969 (Box 53, Folder 720)
  - 69-086-40, 701-141-35, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Choi, Kil Soo, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 721)
  - 66-896-64, 67-938-57, 69-086-65, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Choi, Kyoo Wan, 1966-1970 (Box 53, Folder 722)
  - 72-266-15, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Choo, Kun-Weon, 1972-1973 (Box 53, Folder 723)
  - 68-022-42, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Ham, Eui Keun, 1966-1971 (Box 53, Folder 724)
  - 67-938-52, 68-022-63, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Han, Man Chung, 1967-1971, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 725)
  - 69-086-53, 70-141-24, 70-141-63, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Hong, Kyung Ja, 1969-1973 (Box 53, Folder 726)
  - 68-022-46, 69-086-61, 70-141-42, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Hong (Shim), Yeo-Shin, 1968-1971 (Box 54, Folder 727)
  - 70-141-34, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Chin Whan, 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 728)
  - 70-141-8, 71-203-1,Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Chong Whan, 1970-1973 (Box 54, Folder 729)
  - 66-896-37, 67-938-56, 68-022-62, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Chung-Yong, 1966-1970 (Box 54, Folder 730)
  - 63-694-27, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Han-Seor, 1963-1966, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 731)
  - 68-022-41, 70-141-41A, 69-086-54, 70-141-30, 70-141-39, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Jin Pok, 1968-1972 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - 65-834-27, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Soo Tae, 1965-1967, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 733)
  - 67-938-53, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Yong Il, 1967-1970 (Box 54, Folder 734)
  - 70-141-15, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Young Kyoon, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 735)
  - 71-203-13, 72-266-29, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Kim, Young Min, 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 736)
  - 72-266-29, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Lee, Bong Ja Yun, 1973-1976 (Box 55, Folder 737)
  - 71-203-10, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Lee, Chung Kyoon, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 738)
  - 69-086-50, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Lee, Jae Heung, 1969-1971 (Box 55, Folder 739)
  - 65-834-5, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Lee, Kwang-Ho, 1964-1966 (Box 55, Folder 740)
  - 72-266-29 (L), Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Lee, So Woo, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 741)
  - 70-141-52, 71-141-66, 71-203-36, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Lee, Soon-Hyung, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 742)
  - 67-938-23, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Lee, Young Ja (Yum), 1966-1970 (Box 55, Folder 743)
  - 71-203-2, 72-266-29, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellow, Lee, Won Ro, 1972-1973, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 744)
  - 72-266-29, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellowship Grant, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 745)
  - 72-266-34, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellowship Allocation, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 746)
  - 73-329-19, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellowship Allocation, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 747)
  - 75-343-6, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellowship Grant, 1979-1983 (Box 56, Folder 748)
  - 78-373-8, Seoul National University (SNU), Fellowship Allocation, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 749)
  - 72-245 I, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Field Training Program, 1972-1976 (Box 56, Folder 750)
  - 73-301 I, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1973-1975 (Box 56, Folder 751)
  - 73-321, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Continuing Education Program, 1973, 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 752)
  - 74-333 I, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Postgraduate Education & Research, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1974-1978 (Box 56, Folder 753)
  - 67-935, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Public Health Nurses Training Program, 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 754)
  - 67-969, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 755)
  - 68-008, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Building Construction Equipment, 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 756)
    2014:022, SG 1:036, 2014:022, SG 1:037, 2014:022, SG 1:038
  - 68-008, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Building Construction Equipment, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG 1:036
  - 68-008, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Building Construction Equipment, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG 1:037
    Oversized architectural drawings
  - 68-008, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Building Construction Equipment, 1968-1970; 2014:022, SG 1:038
    Oversized Architectural drawing
  - 68-031, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Faculty Training, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1971 (Box 56, Folder 757)
  - 68-032, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Equipment, Serology-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 758)
  - 69-098, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Research, 1969, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 759)
  - 70-125, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1971, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 760)
  - 70-135, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 56, Folder 761)
  - 72-274, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 762)
  - 72-274 II, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Invoices & Shipping, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 763)
  - 70-119, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Consultant, Brown, Harold W., 1970-1971 (Box 57, Folder 764)
  - 72-234, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Consultant, Brown, Harold W., Public Health Education, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 765)
  - 71-211, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Public Health Field Training, 1971-1973 (Box 57, Folder 766)
  - 70-141-47, 71-203-8, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Fellow, Han, Dal Sun, 1970-1973 (Box 57, Folder 767)
  - 72-266-10Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Fellow, Noon, Ok Ryun, 1972-1974 (Box 57, Folder 768)
  - 70-141-1, 70-141-50, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Fellow, Rhee, Seon Ja, 1968-1972 (Box 57, Folder 769)
  - 73-318-11, Seoul National University (SNU), School of Public Health, Fellowship Allocation, 1974, 1976-1978 (Box 57, Folder 770)
  - 74-337 I, Seoul National University (SNU), Department of Nursing, Teaching Programs, 1974, 1976-1979 (Box 57, Folder 771)
  - 72-266-35, Seoul National University (SNU), Department of Nursing, Fellowship Allocation, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 772)
  - 75-343 (35A), Seoul National University (SNU), Department of Nursing, Fellowship Allocation, 1977-1980 (Box 57, Folder 773)
  - 78-373-3, Seoul National University (SNU), Nursing, Fellowship Allocation, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 774)
  - 72-246 I, Seoul National University (SNU), Department of Nursing, Support, 1972-1976 (Box 58, Folder 775)
  - Severance Union Medical College, General, 1953-1958, 1960, 1967, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 776)
  - CM 327-4, Severance Union Medical College, Fellow, Park, Soo Yun, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 777)
  - CM 327-20, Severance Union Medical College, Fellow, Soh, Chin Thack, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 778)
  - CM 327-16, Severance Union Medical College, Fellow, Yun, Duk Jin, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 779)
  - CM 343, Severance Union Medical College, Books & Laboratory Equipment, 1956-1960 (Box 58, Folder 780)
  - Yonsei University, Individual, Rice, Roberta G., General Correspondence, 1962-1974 (Box 58, Folder 781)
  - Yonsei University, Individual, Weiss, Ernest W., General Correspondence, 1964, 1966, 1969-1976 (Box 58, Folder 782)
  - CM 394, 58-426, 61-571, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, 1959-1964 (Box 58, Folder 783)
  - CM 394, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, Master Plan, 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 784)
    2014:022, SG 1:039, 2014:022, SG 1:040
  - CM 394, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, Master Plan, 2014:022. SG 1:039
  - CM 394, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, Master Plan, 1959-1960; 2014:022, SG 1:040
    oversized architectural drawing
  - CM 394, 58-469, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, 1956-1959 (Box 58, Folder 785)
  - CM 394, 58-469, 61-571, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, United Board-Invoices & Correspondence, National Council of Churches, 1961-1963, 1965, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 786)
  - CM 394, 58-469, 61-571, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, 1960-1961 (Box 59, Folder 787)
    2014:022, SG 1:041
  - CM 394, 58-469, 61-571, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, 1960-1961; 2014:022, SG 1:041
  - 58-469, 61-571, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, General Correspondence, 1961-1963, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 788-189)
    2014:022, SG 1:042
  - 58-469, 61-571, Yonsei University, Building Construction & Equipment, General Correspondence, 1961-1962, 1965; 2014:022, SG 1:042
  - 57-397-23, Hirosaki University, Fellow, Matsunaga, Fujio, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 790)
  - 59-478, Hokkaido University, Books, 1959-1963 (Box 59, Folder 791)
  - 59-501, Hokkaido University, Equipment-Physiology Department, 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 792)
  - 61-602, Hokkaido University, Equipment-Cardiology, 1961-1964 (Box 59, Folder 793)
  - 67-938-46, Hokkaido University, Fellow, Hoshino, Taekshi, 1964, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 794)
  - 66-896-19, Hokkaido University, Fellow, Kodama, George, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 795)
  - 68-022-25, Hokkaido University, Fellow, Kodama, Takao, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 796)
  - 66-896-34, Hokkaido University, Fellow, Murakami, Tadashi, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 797)
  - 65-834-33, Hokkaido University, Fellow, Sato, Aiko, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 798)
  - 63-694-21, Hokkaido University, Fellow, Sugie, Saburo, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 799)
  - 60-541-21, Hokkaido University, Fellow, Suwa, Nozomi, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 800)
  - CM 362-10, Hokkaido University, Fellow, Torii, Toshio, 1956, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 801)
  - Keio University, General, 1966, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 802)
  - CM 384, Keio University, General Correspondence & Invoices, 1956-1959 (Box 59, Folder 803)